

MOBILE APPS DEVELOPER

Yogyakarta, 55181

0

+6281327183215



ajiedwi4798@gmail.com

## LINKS

Portfolio:

https://ajiedwi.github.io

Linkedin:

http://www.linkedin.com/in/ajiedwi/

Github:

https://github.com/ajiedwi

Medium:

https://medium.com/@ajiedwi

# SKILLS

Kotlin

Mobile Apps Development

**Apps Development** 

Git

NodeJS

React Native

Restful API

# LANGUAGES

- O Indonesia
- o English

## **ABOUT ME**

Driven and determined software engineer, promoting 6 years of experience in building client applications. Versatile software engineer works well both as part of team and independently. Offers strong interpersonal and communication skills. Highly educated with capability to deliver on key project milestones. Seeking to secure an engineering role with internationally astute firm involved in any industry.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER ANDROID | MAR 2022 - PRESENT

#### MOLADIN, JAKARTA

As a Mid Software Engineer - Android, I work close with other Stakeholder (UI/UX, BE, and Product teams) to convert any business requirement into a feature that run in any android devices. Moreover, I have responsibility to review and estimate tasks that given by the Product teams before proceed them. I also have to provide a high quality and documented code that has been tested with unit tests to ensures that the product delivered to the users has a minimum level of crashes and bugs. My role including to guide a Junior Software Engineer to deliver more tasks well and swift.

Helping Moladin to increase the number of sales by working on giving product recommendation, rating and comment to agent, and any other features.

( ) SOFTWARE ENGINEER ANDROID - FREELANCE | DEC 2021 - MAR 2022

### MOLADIN, JAKARTA

As a freelance Android Software Engineer, I helping out the Engineer to help get their tasks done.

ANDROID DEVELOPER | SEP 2019 - MAR 2022

# TECHNOPARTNER INDONESIA, YOGYAKARTA

Here I responsible for develop and deploy mobile applications (Android) with clean, reusable, and high quality code written in Kotlin and Java. Mostly, I worked on Food and Beverage order and delivering field applications. Here I responsible for develop and deploy mobile applications (Android) with clean, reusable, and high quality code written in Kotlin and Java. Mostly, I worked on Food and Beverage order and delivering field applications.

ANDROID DEVELOPER | SEP 2018 - SEP 2019

## KREASI KODE, YOGYAKARTA

I responsible to develop mobile application (Android) written in many stack such as Java, Kotlin and React Native (Javascript) and release them to Google Play Store. Mostly I worked in tourism application field here.

● IT SUPPORT | MAR 2017 - SEP 2019

## MUSEUM SONOBUDOYO, YOGYAKARTA

Supporting the Sonobudoyo Museum in the IT field such as developing a guest book application, developing a note-taking application to helping them move their collection, and developing apps to facilitate their national exhibition.

APPS DEVELOPER | MAR 2017 - PRESENT

## SELF EMPLOYED, YOGYAKARTA

Not limited only to Android Application, I'm also capable to build any other stack of Application (BE, FE).

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR | 2019